Hey, you guys wanna go
on a real live quest?
(Sheldon:)Outside? I just made cocoa.
Oh, come on, it'll be fun.
(Howard:)What is it?
(Leonard:)Do you guys remember
Penny's ex-boyfriend Kurt?
(Leonard:)Yeah, that's him.
Uh, it turns out he owes Penny a lot
of money and I'm gonna go get it from him.
Who's with me?
(Howard:)Ooh, double sixes.
(Penny:)Really?
You're just gonna let me go by myself?
(Raj:)Oh, cool, I got a sword.
(Leonard:)I could use some help.
(Howard:)Here.
(Leonard:)You guys are unbelievable.
(Leonard:)You play a game to simulate adventure,
but when there's adventure...
(Leonard:)...in the real world you just wimp out.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, do you not recall the last time
we visited this gentleman?
(Sheldon:)We returned home without pants.
(Leonard:)- I do.
- Are you sure?
(Sheldon:)Because your proposal suggests
that you don't.
(Leonard:)I'm not afraid of him.